Guide to the Davis Family Papers, 1876-2007 and undated, bulk 1924-2004 RL.00291
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Writings Series, 1889-2007 and undated, 2 boxes
  - Davis, Nancy Elizabeth (1924-2004)
    Granddaughter of Andrew Davis and Frances Nash, and daughter of Harry Winifred Davis and Elizabeth Levy Davis. Born in Washington, D.C. and attended Howard University. After studies at Pratt Institute, she returned to Washington and taught art in the D.C. public schools, retiring in 1975.
    - 2004 Mar. (Box 7)
  - Davis, Thulani
    - Articles by, 1971-1981 (Box 7)
    - Articles by, 1992-1994, 2003 (Box 7)
    - Clippings, 1977-1980 and undated (Box 7)
    - Clippings, 1984-1986 (Box 7)
    - Clippings, 1992-1994 (Box 7)
    - Clippings and programs, 1996-2006 (Box 7)
    - Life Magazine, 1992 [located in back of box 7] (Box 7)
    - Miscellaneous materials, undated (Box 7)
      - "Fanfare for the Warrior," with 4 parts of Davis' radio show, 2 audiocassettes (Box 7, Audio-cassette RL-00291-CS-0001, Audio-cassette RL-00291-CS-0002)
  - Davis, William Roscoe
    - Materials, 1950-1991 (Box 7)
  - Stone Family
    - Family tree, genealogy (Box 7)
    - Family reunions, 1991-1994 (Box 7)
  - Gray, Dorothy Mealey (1908-circa 2000)
    Dorothy Mealey Gray was the granddaughter of Emma Jane Davis and John Mealey. She earned degrees in sociology and psychology from Northeastern University and worked as child welfare supervisor in the Taunton, Massachusetts Department of Public Welfare.
    - Various papers, circa 1990 (Box 7)
  - Neal, Georgia Campbell
    - 1889 May, 1972 Feb., 1982 Nov., and undated (Box 7)
  - Peake, Mary S.
    Mary S. Peake (1823-1862) was the teacher at the first school for blacks in Hampton, Virginia, which started in 1861 under the auspices of the American Missionary Association. This school was a predecessor of Hampton Institute. Before the Civil War she taught William Roscoe Davis.
    - Undated materials (Box 7)
  - Young, Davis C.
    Davis C. Young (1948-1997) was the great-grandson of William Roscoe Davis. He was born in Norfolk, Virginia, earned degrees from Dartmouth College, Williams College, and Rutgers University, and worked in the banking industry. His father, P. B. Young, was editor and publisher of the Norfolk Journal and Guide newspaper.
    - Materials, 1997 June (Box 7)